# Dawson **Hamilton**

Web Developer

Address 356 E 4115 S, Apt 231, Salt Lake City, UT,

84107

Phone (385) 274-8009

E-mail dawsondhamilton@gmail.com

My goal is to become a full time full stack Web Developer. To accomplish this I am a solution-driven professional excelling in highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to challenges and focused on customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused web sites using HTML, CSS, JQuery, PHP and JavaScript. Experience building products for desktop, phone and mobile app users, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, usability and speed. Responding to challenges by designing and developing solutions and building web applications aligned to customer's services. Translating solutions into code and working across many different APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

#### **Skills**

Great at collaborating with others	Very Good
Agile workflow processes	Excellent
Programming	Very Good
Work great under pressure	Excellent

# **Work History**

2016-06 - Current

#### Server

Cracker Barrel, West Valley City, UT

- Enhanced operational efficiency by using slow periods to restock employee and customer supplies, including ice, condiments, utensils, napkins, trays and delivery bags.
- Collaborated with kitchen team to support order preparation, manage efficient deliveries and minimize customer service issues by verifying meals.
- Worked with POS system to place orders, manage bills and handle complimentary items for dissatisfied customers.
- Trained incoming staff on restaurant's practices, culture and procedures to maximize job satisfaction and productivity.
- Helped customers place orders, explained menu items and suggested appropriate options for food allergy concerns.

2019-02 - 2019-07	Teacher Assistant
2017-02 - 2017-07	TEUCHEL ASSISTANT

West valley Fire Academy, West Valley City, UT

• Tutored and supported students individually and in groups of up to 35 by reteaching and reviewing lesson concepts and mastering skills.

### **Education**

2018-09 - 2019-01 Some College (No Degree): Firefighting

West Valley Fire Academy - West Valley City, UT

2013-08 - 2016-01 High School Diploma

American International School of Utah - Murray, UT

#### Software



## Certifications

2019-01	Firefighter I

2019-01 Firefighter II

2019-01 Hazardous Materials Awareness

**2019-01** Hazardous Materials Operations